# Lam Yuen Ho Joseph

Passionate software engineer with 2+ years of experience in a multi-cultural environment. Willing to learn and provide ideas while pursuing the latest technologies to improve the workflow.

Email: yuenholam@gmail.com Mobile: +852 91726708 GitHub: github.com/JosephLYH Address: Hong Kong

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/lam-yuen-ho-joseph

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **ASMPT Limited**

# Software Engineer

06/2022 - Present

- Rewrote the deep learning pipeline to utilize GPU speedup to achieve 5x speedup in training time utilizing distributed training, GPU acceleration, and mixed-precision training
- Designed, implemented and maintained software for creating artificial training data with finetuned inpainting models, generating 300+ samples/h without GPU
- Jointly designed and implemented high speed segmentation models to achieve 50% higher throughput
- Implemented features and maintained software in C/C++ and Lua
- Automation scripts and configurations for triggering data pipeline and AI model training for use by product team

# Hong Kong Applied Science and Technology Research Institute (ASTRI)

### Summer Intern

06/2021 - 08/2021

- Built backend servers for hosting AI models using Python, Flask, Docker, MongoDB, MySQL, AWS, Anaconda and conduct testing with Postman
- Implemented APIs for initiating training, uploading and downloading a trained model
- Frontend web development using React.js

### **ROBOT DATA CO. LTD**

#### Intern

09/2017 - 09/2018

- Assisted in data collection for chatbots and computer vision AI
- Created visualization using PowerBI and Tableau
- Assisted technical support for clients

### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Engineering)

The University of Hong Kong

09/2018 - 06/2022

- Second Class Honours (Division One)
- Dean's Honors List 2020 2021
- General Secretary of Swire Hall Student's Association, Session 2019 2020

- Financial Secretary of Joint Hall Cultural Committee, Session 2019 2020
- Team captain of Swire Hall Squash Team

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

### Captcha breaking court booking AI

- To book courts early in the morning automatically for hall sports teams
- Wrote script to crawl the website to get training data, trained and deployed the AI in 3 days

### Discord bot integration with Stable diffusion

• Integrated stable diffusion into discord bots for use in private servers

### **SKILLS**

### **Programming Languages**

• Python, C/C++, Lua, Shell, SQL, Java, HTML, CSS, Javascript

### **Frameworks and Tools**

• PyTorch, TensorFlow, Docker, Flask, Django, MongoDB, MySQL, AWS, Anaconda, Redis, Kafka

# **CERTIFICATES**

• Microsoft Professional Program Data Science Certificate (02/2018)

# **LANGUAGES**

- Cantonese
- English
- Mandarin